Guide to the Alfred E. Kahn papers, 1942-1994
Kahn, Alfred E. papers, 1942-1994
- Series IX. Speeches
  - Pittsburgh, PA 10/30/80, 1980 (Box 120, Folder 9)
  - Miscellaneous Briefings, 1980 (Box 120, Folder 10)
  - Industrial Organization Review (9), 1974 (Box 120, Folder 11)
  - Economic Issues-1964 and Milton Friedman vs Me, 1964 (Box 120, Folder 12)
  - Speeches, 1970s (Box 120, Folder 13)
  - Speeches - Ecology, 1971 (Box 120, Folder 14)
  - Dean-Speeches, 1973 (Box 120, Folder 15)
  - Union Monopoly - General, 1970s (Box 120, Folder 16)
  - Monopoly at Law (Notes Used), 1959 (Box 120, Folder 17)
  - Price Discrimination, 1967 (Box 120, Folder 18)
  - The Tyranny of Small Decisions, 1972 (Box 120, Folder 19)
  - Kahn - Confidential, 1974 (Box 120, Folder 20)
  - American Economic Review Board of Editors, 1968 (Box 120, Folder 21)
  - Lake Cayuga, 1968 (Box 120, Folder 22)
  - Vitae, 1969 (Box 120, Folder 23)
  - Vertical Integration, 1960 (Box 120, Folder 24)
  - SRA P.L. 480, 1962 (Box 120, Folder 25)
  - Taiwan, 1960s (Box 120, Folder 26)
  - US Balance of Payments, 1966 (Box 120, Folder 27)
  - Fulbright, etc., 1965 (Box 120, Folder 28)
  - National Econ. Research Assoc., Inc., 1973 (Box 120, Folder 29)
  - CEA Memos, 1956 (Box 120, Folder 30)
  - 351 Guideposts, 1964 (Box 120, Folder 31)
  - 352 Guideposts, 1989 (Box 120, Folder 32)
  - 651 Antitrust Survey, 1989 (Box 120, Folder 33)
- Series X. Publications
  - Am. Economic Review "Deficiencies of Am. Patent Law", Sept., 1940, 1940 (Box 59, Folder 1)
  - Am. Economic Review "Palestine: A Problem in Economic Evaluation", Sept., 1944, 1944 (Box 59, Folder 2)
  - Quart. Jour. of Econom. British Bal. of Payments & Problems, May, 1947, 1947 (Box 59, Folder 3)
  - The Structure of Am. Industry "The Chemical Industry" Chapt VI, 1948 (Box 59, Folder 4)
  - Am. Econom. Review "The Burden of Import Duties: Comment", Dec., 1948, 1948 (Box 59, Folder 5)
  - Am. Jour. Econ. & Socio. "Price Discrimination in Law & Economics", Apr., 1952, 1952 (Box 59, Folder 6)
  - Journal of Political Eco. "Antitrust Law & the Big Buyer: Another Look at the A&P Case", Apr., 1952, 1952 (Box 59, Folder 7)
  - Yale Law Journal "Leadership and Conflict in the Pricing of Gasoline", June, 1952, 1952 (Box 59, Folder 8)
  - Am. Economic Review, Review of "Basing-Point Pricing Systems…", Sept., 1952, 1952 (Box 59, Folder 9)
  - Indiana Law Journal "Integration & Dissolution of the A&P Company" Fall, 1953, 1953 (Box 59, Folder 10)
  - Jour. of Pol. Econ. "A Reply" (to M. Adelman), Oct., 1953, 1953 (Box 59, Folder 11)
  - Harvard Law Review "Standards for Antitrust Policy", Nov., 1953, 1953 (Box 59, Folder 12)
  - Yale Law Journal "A legal & Economic Appraisal of the 'New' Sherman & Clayton Acts", Jan., 1954, 1954 (Box 59, Folder 13)
  - Banca Nazionale Del Lavoro Quart. Review "Reg. of Crude Oil Prod. in the US & lessons for Italy", June, 1955, 1955 (Box 59, Folder 14)
  - Antitrust Bulletin " My Antitrust Philosophy: Evidence of Schizophrenia or Shattering", Nov., 1955, 1955 (Box 59, Folder 15)
  - Competition, Cartels & Their Reg. "The Role of Patents" Chapter 8, 1955 (Box 59, Folder 16)
  - AEA Papers & Proceedings "Economic Issues in Reg. Field Price of Natural Gas", May, 1960, 1960 (Box 59, Folder 17)
  - Jour. of Am. Econ. Assoc. "Economic Issues in Reg. Field Price of Natural Gas.", May, 1960, 1960 (Box 59, Folder 18)
  - Hearings: State of Economy & Policy for Full Employment "Market Power & Econ. Growth…", Aug., 1962, 1962 (Box 59, Folder 19)
  - Quart. Jour. of Econom. "Agricultural Aid & Economic Devel. The Case of Israel", Nov., 1962, 1962 (Box 59, Folder 20)
  - Am. Econ. Review "Depletion Allowance in the Context of Cartelization", June, 1964, 1964 (Box 59, Folder 21)
  - Clippings 1985, 1985 (Box 59, Folder 22)
  - Clippings 1986, 1986 (Box 59, Folder 23)
  - Clippings 1987, 1987 (Box 59, Folder 24)
  - Clippings 1988, 1988 (Box 59, Folder 25)
  - "The Tyranny of Small Decisions: Market Failures, Imperfections, And The Limits of Economics", 1966 (Box 60, Folder 1)
  - "Cartels and Trade Associations" Int'l Encyclopedia of the Social Sciences, 1968 (Box 60, Folder 2)
  - Yale Law Journal "Merits of Reserving Cost-Savings from Domestic Comm. Satellites", Jan., 1968, 1968 (Box 60, Folder 3)
  - Jour. of Am. Econ. Assoc. "Graduated Fair Return: Comment", Mar., 1968, 1968 (Box 60, Folder 4)
  - Natural Resources Journal "The Combined Effects of Prorationing, the Depletion Allowance and Import Quotas on the Cost of Producing Crude Oil in the US", Jan., 1970, 1970 (Box 60, Folder 5)
  - Amer. Econ. Rev.: Papers & Proceed "National Communications Policy: Discussion", 1970 (Box 60, Folder 6)
  - Land Economics "Dual Pricing in Southern Louisiana: A Reply", Aug., 1970, 1970 (Box 60, Folder 7)
  - P.I.P National Environmental Press Seminar "The Economics of the Electricity-Environmental Issue: a Primer", 1972 (Box 60, Folder 8)
  - Journal of Economic Issues "Economic Theory as a Guideline for Government Intervention and Control: Comment", June, 1974, 1974 (Box 60, Folder 9)
  - "Market Power Inflation: A Conceptual Overview", 1975 (Box 60, Folder 10)
  - "Efficient Rate Design: The Transition from Theory to Practice", Apr., 1975, 1975 (Box 60, Folder 11)
  - "Load Control, Resource Conservation, and King Charles' Head", May 19, 1977, 1977 (Box 60, Folder 12)
  - Public Utilities Reports "An Economist at Work on Utility Rate Regulation", 1978 (Box 60, Folder 13)
  - "Airline Deregulation: Getting from Here to There", 1978 (Box 60, Folder 14)
  - Applications of Economics to an Imperfect World (AEK), May, 1979, 1979 (Box 60, Folder 15)
  - "A Paean to Legal Creativity" Administrative Law Review, Winter 1979, 1979 (Box 60, Folder 16)
  - "A Conversation w/ AEK" 4/3/80, 1980 (Box 60, Folder 17)
  - "Why We Oppose Mandatory Wage & Price Controls" (AEK), Oct., 1980, 1980 (Box 60, Folder 18)
  - Ethical Values in a Market System nera Topics, Jan., 1981, 1981 (Box 60, Folder 19)
  - A New Approach to the Economics of Health Care Health Care Economics: Paths to, 1981 (Box 60, Folder 20)
  - Can Liberalism Survive Inflation? The Economist, Mar., 1981, 1981 (Box 60, Folder 21)
  - Lowell Lecture: Must We Live With Inflation Through the 1980s? Harvard 4/30/81, 1981 (Box 60, Folder 22)
  - Dixville Notch II, Pricing of Tele. Terminal Equip. Draft for Comment, June, 1981, 1981 (Box 60, Folder 23)
  - "Reforming Gov't Reg.: recent progress in the U.S." 6/9/81, 1981 (Box 60, Folder 24)
  - "Utility Regulation Revisited" nera topics 6/15/81, 1981 (Box 60, Folder 25)
  - Interview w/ AEK, A&S Newsletter Cornell, Fall 1981, 1981 (Box 60, Folder 26)
  - "Is Inflation Abating?" nera topics, Nov., 1981, 1981 (Box 60, Folder 27)
  - "Liberals Must Face the Facts" Challenge Nov.-Dec., 1981, 1981 (Box 60, Folder 28)
  - "Regulation & Imagination" MGIC Newsletter Nov.-Dec., 1981, 1981 (Box 60, Folder 29)
  - "The New Merger Wave" nera topics, Dec., 1981, 1981 (Box 60, Folder 30)
  - "A Regulator Speaks Out" Channel Mag., Dec., 1981-Jan., 1982, 1981-1982 (Box 60, Folder 31)
  - "Transportation"-Regulation Mag., Jan.-Feb., 1982, 1982 (Box 60, Folder 32)
  - Patterson Lecture: The Airline Industry, Is It Time to Regulate, Apr., 1982, 1982 (Box 60, Folder 33)
  - The Political Feasibility of Regulatory Reform: How Did We Do It?, 1982 (Box 60, Folder 34)
  - Journal of Policy Analysis and Management "A Comment on Wahl's Argument", 1982 (Box 60, Folder 35)
  - Some Thoughts on Telephone Access Pricing - Sept., 1982, 1982 (Box 60, Folder 36)
  - "The Regulatory Agenda" Telecom Access & Public Policy, Sept., 1982, 1982 (Box 60, Folder 37)
  - Bk.Review, Breyer's Regulation and Its Reform, Bell Journal, Fall 1982, 1982 (Box 60, Folder 38)
  - "Is It Time to Re-reg. Air Ind.?" World Economy, London, Dec., 1982, 1982 (Box 60, Folder 39)
  - "The Regulatory Agenda" Published in "Telecome.Access", 1982 (Box 60, Folder 40)
  - Deregulation: Its Meaning and Implications for Antitrust Enforcement NY Bar Assoc, 1982 (Box 60, Folder 41)
  - Utility Diversification, from Energy Journal, Jan., 1983, 1983 (Box 60, Folder 42)
  - "Some Thoughts on Telephone Access Pricing", Apr., 1983, 1983 (Box 60, Folder 43)
  - The Passing of the Public Utility Concept, May, 1983, 1983 (Box 60, Folder 44)
  - Noam BK: The Passing of the Public Utility Concept: A Reprise, Aug., 1983, 1983 (Box 60, Folder 45)
  - "Deregulation&Vested Interests: The Case of The Airlines" The Political Economy of Dereg., 1983 (Box 60, Folder 46)
  - The Relevance of Ind. Organ., 1983 (Box 60, Folder 47)
  - Economic Policies For the 80s, Nov., 1983, 1983 (Box 60, Folder 48)
  - A Needed Dose of Competition Challenge, Apr., 1984, 1984 (Box 60, Folder 49)
  - Yale Journal on Reg. Road to More Intell. Telephone Pricing, May, 1984, 1984 (Box 60, Folder 50)
  - PUF Next Step in Telecommunications Regulation and Research 7/19/84, 1984 (Box 60, Folder 51)
  - Telematics The Uneasy Marriage of Regulation and Competition, Sept., 1984, 1984 (Box 60, Folder 52)
  - Macro Consequences of Sensible Micro Policies AEA Dallas 12/28/84, 1984 (Box 60, Folder 53)
  - The Regulatory Agenda/Concluding Comments (in Telecommunications Access and Public Policy), 1984 (Box 60, Folder 54)
  - Industrial Policy & Deregulation Federal Bar News&Journal, Jan., 1985, 1985 (Box 60, Folder 55)
  - "Telecom. Regulation: Impact of Tech. on Soc. Inst. Future Direction in E.E." 6/12/85, 1985 (Box 60, Folder 56)
  - NSF Comments, 1985 (Box 61, Folder 1)
  - The Conference Board "Antitrust in Transition: Two Dialogues", 1985 (Box 61, Folder 2)
  - Antitrust Law Journal "The Theory and Application of Regulation" Apr., 1986, 1986 (Box 61, Folder 3)
  - The Tyranny of Small Decisions and the Perils of Big Ones (Cornell in Washington Symposium) 5/20/86, 1986 (Box 61, Folder 4)
  - ITT Lecture Series "Future of Local Tel. Service", 1986 (Box 61, Folder 5)
  - "How to Survive Economic Dereg." Penn State 10/2/86, 1986 (Box 61, Folder 6)
  - Article Yale J. on Reg. (Shew) "Current Issues in Telecom. Regulation: Pricing", 1987 (Box 61, Folder 7)
  - "Transportation Deregulation…And All That" Econ. Dev. Quart., 1987 (Box 61, Folder 8)
  - "The Future of Local Telephone Serv." Bell Atlantic Quarterly, Spring 1987, 1987 (Box 61, Folder 9)
  - Calif. Law Review "Deregulatory Schizophrenia" May, 1987, 1987 (Box 61, Folder 10)
  - "The Future of Local Telephone Serv…" Wharton School June, 1987, 1987 (Box 61, Folder 11)
  - Ohio Council on Economic Education Highlights, Autumn, 1987, 1987 (Box 61, Folder 12)
  - "Thoughts on the Past, Present…of Telecommunications…" 10/5/87, 1987 (Box 61, Folder 13)
  - Thinking About the Deregulation Record 11/4/87-11/5/87, 1987 (Box 61, Folder 14)
  - Article "Joint Council on Econ. Educ." Spring, 1988, 1988 (Box 61, Folder 15)
  - Competition: Past, Present and Future - Perception vs. Reality, Mar., 1988, 1988 (Box 61, Folder 16)
  - American Economic Review "Surprises From Deregulation" May, 1988, 1988 (Box 61, Folder 17)
  - Airline Deregulation - A Mixed Bag But a Clear Success Nevertheless, Spring 1988, 1988 (Box 61, Folder 18)
  - Regulation: I Would Do it Again, Fall 1988, 1988 (Box 61, Folder 19)
  - In Defense of Deregulation (In Cleared For Takeoff), 1988 (Box 61, Folder 20)
  - Innovative Pricing of Electricity NIMO/EPRI 9/28/88, 1988 (Box 61, Folder 21)
  - Deregulation: Past, Present and Future, Fall 1988, 1988 (Box 61, Folder 22)
  - Efficient Pricing of Congested Airport Facilities, Apr. 1989, 1989 (Box 61, Folder 23)
  - Do We Need to Curb Investments Foreigners are Making in the US?, 1989 (Box 61, Folder 24)
  - Yale Journal Article "Dereg: Looking Forward & Backward" Spring 1990, 1990 (Box 61, Folder 25)
  - UPF Telecom., Competitiveness & Eco. Development--What Makes Us… Sept. 1990, 1990 (Box 61, Folder 26)
  - "Thinking About Predation" Review of Industrial Organization, 1991 (Box 61, Folder 27)
  - The Changing Focus of Electric Util. Regulation, 1991 (Box 61, Folder 28)
  - Elec. Jour. "Rational Least-Cost Planning", 1991 (Box 61, Folder 29)
  - Book: What is to be Done? "Price Dereg., Corporatization and Competition" Feb., 1991, 1991 (Box 61, Folder 30)
  - The Soviet Economic Crisis: Steps to Avert Collapse Feb., 1991, 1991 (Box 61, Folder 31)
  - "The Case For Bell Operating Company Competition in Information Services" nera topics, Apr., 1991, 1991 (Box 61, Folder 32)
  - The Electricity Journal: An Exchange of Views, July 1991, 1991 (Box 61, Folder 33)
  - What is to be Done? "Proposals for the Soviet Transition", 1992 (Box 61, Folder 34)
  - I'industria Regolamentazone e Concorrenza Nella Imprese di Pubblica…. 4/1/92, 1992 (Box 61, Folder 35)
  - Anti-trust Law Journal Market Power Issues, May 1992, 1992 (Box 61, Folder 36)
  - Resources and Energy Vol. 14 "Least Cost Planning Generally and DSM in Particular", 1992 (Box 61, Folder 37)
  - Cornell Alumni News "Why Airline Deregulation Works" June, 1992, 1992 (Box 61, Folder 38)
  - CRI Incentive Regulation, RPI-X, June-July, 1992, 1992 (Box 61, Folder 39)
  - Review of Industrial Organization "Pricing of Tele. Serv: A Comment", 1993 (Box 61, Folder 40)
  - Review of Ind. Organization "The Comp. Consq. of Hub Dominance" Aug., 1993, 1993 (Box 61, Folder 41)
  - Aviation Week: "A Mixed Review For Regulation" 8/16/93, 1993 (Box 61, Folder 42)
  - Federal Bar News & Journal "National Commission to Ensure a Strong Competitive Airline Ind." Nov.-Dec., 1993, 1993 (Box 61, Folder 43)
  - The Fortune Encyclopedia of Econ. "Airline Deregulation", 1993 (Box 62, Folder 1)
  - Regulation Mag. "Change, Challenge and Competition: A Review ACR", 1993 (Box 62, Folder 2)
  - Public Utilities Report "Competition in the Electric is Inevitable and Desirable", 1994 (Box 62, Folder 3)
  - Yale Jor. on Reg. "The Pricing of Inputs Sold to Competitions: A Comment" Spring, 1994, 1994 (Box 62, Folder 4)
  - Electricity JRNL "Can Reg. & Comp. Coexist?" Oct., 1994, 1994 (Box 62, Folder 5)
  - The Pricing of Inputs Sold to Competition: A Comment YJ, 1994 (Box 62, Folder 6)
  - Article Baumol/Joskow/Kahn "The Challenge for Federal and State Regulators…" Dec., 1994, 1994 (Box 62, Folder 7)
  - EEI-Transition from Reg. to Efficient Competition in Electric Power, 1995 (Box 62, Folder 8)
  - "Competition in the Electric Industry Offers Promise and Challenge" June, 1995, 1995 (Box 62, Folder 9)
  - Economic Society of Australia "Dereg. Of the Public Util. Transitional Problems and Solutions" Sept., 1995, 1995 (Box 62, Folder 10)
  - Reseaux: Deregulation Des Services Publics, Oct., 1995, 1995 (Box 62, Folder 11)
  - Regulation "Thirteen Steps to Reconciliation", 1996 (Box 62, Folder 12)
  - Statement on the Breakfast Cereals Industry 3/11/96, 1996 (Box 62, Folder 13)
  - Policy Analysis "How to Treat the Costs…" 11/27/96, 1996 (Box 62, Folder 14)
  - Article: Natural Resources Jrl. Based on U. of N.M., Winter 1997, 1997 (Box 62, Folder 15)
  - Article: The Electricity Journal "Electric Deregulation", 1998 (Box 62, Folder 16)
  - Deregulation: Micromanaging the Entry and Survival of Competitors, Feb., 1998, 1998 (Box 62, Folder 17)
  - Book Letting Go: … MSU Inst. Public Util., Spring 1998, 1998 (Box 62, Folder 18)
  - Regulators' Revenge "Resisting the Temptation to Micromanage" Cato Institute, 1998 (Box 62, Folder 19)
  - J. Air Transport Mgmt. "Comments on Exclusionary Airline Pricing" pp. 1-12, 1999 (Box 62, Folder 20)
  - The Electricity Journal "Bribing Customers to Leave…" (Guest Editorial), 1999 (Box 62, Folder 21)
  - ACI 8th Regional Conference Keynote Address Las Vegas 10/25/99, 1999 (Box 62, Folder 22)
  - "The Telecommunications Act at Three Years: An Economic Eval…" Kahn, Tardiff, Weisman, Dec., 1999, 1999 (Box 62, Folder 23)
  - Public Utility Fortnightly "Standard Ratepayers…" 6/1/2001, 2001 (Box 62, Folder 24)
  - Whom the Gods would Destroy, or How Not to Deregulate, 2001 (Box 62, Folder 25)
  - Journal of Regulatory Economics "Deregulatory Tar Baby" Jan., 2002, 2002 (Box 62, Folder 26)
  - "The Adequacy of Prospective Returns on Generation Investments Under Price Control Mechanisms" nera topics, Feb., 2002, 2002 (Box 62, Folder 27)
  - "How to Make Regulation Work", 2002 (Box 62, Folder 28)
  - AEI-Brookings "Lessons From Deregulation…", 2004 (Box 62, Folder 29)
  - Infrastructure 45(1) "A Morning with Dr. Alfred Kahn, Part 2", 2005 (Box 62, Folder 30)
  - Journal on Telecom. & High Tech. Law "The Digital Broadband Migration" Vol. 4, Feb., 2006, 2006 (Box 62, Folder 31)
  - Journal on Telecom. & High Tech. Law "The Digital Broadband Migration" Vol. 5, Feb., 2006, 2006 (Box 62, Folder 32)
  - "A Democratic Voice of Caution on Network Neutrality" Oct., 2006, 2006 (Box 62, Folder 33)
  - AEI-Brookings "Network Neutrality" Mar., 2007, 2007 (Box 62, Folder 34)
  - AEI Regulatory Markets "The Threat of Latter Day 'Progressives' to an Authentically Liberal Economic Policy", Jan. 2008, 2008 (Box 62, Folder 35)
  - "Reflections of an Unwitting 'Political Entrepreneur'" Dec., 2008, 2008 (Box 62, Folder 36)
- >Series XI. Correspondence
  - A-C, 1982-83 (Box 67, Folder 1)
  - D-K, 1982-83 (Box 67, Folder 2)
  - L-P, 1982-83 (Box 67, Folder 3)
  - Q-Smiley, 1982-83 (Box 67, Folder 4)
  - Smith-Z, 1982-83 (Box 67, Folder 5)
  - A, 1990s (Box 69, Folder 1)
  - B-1, 1990s (Box 69, Folder 2)
  - B-2, 1990s (Box 69, Folder 3)
  - C, 1990s (Box 69, Folder 4)
  - D, 1990s (Box 69, Folder 5)
  - E, 1990s (Box 69, Folder 6)
  - F, 1990s (Box 69, Folder 7)
  - G, 1990s (Box 70, Folder 1)
  - H-1, 1990s (Box 70, Folder 2)
  - H-2, 1990s (Box 70, Folder 3)
  - I, 1990s (Box 70, Folder 4)
  - J, 1990s (Box 70, Folder 5)
  - M-3, 1990s (Box 70, Folder 6)
  - K-1, 1990s (Box 71, Folder 1)
  - K-2, 1990s (Box 71, Folder 2)
  - L, 1990s (Box 71, Folder 3)
  - M-1, 1990s (Box 71, Folder 4)
  - M-2, 1990s (Box 71, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence w/ Joel Dirlam (1), 1991 (Box 71, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence w/ Joel Dirlam (2), 2005 (Box 71, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence w/ Joel Dirlam (3), 1985 (Box 71, Folder 8)
  - N-1, 1990s (Box 72, Folder 1)
  - N-2, 1990s (Box 72, Folder 2)
  - N-3, 1990s (Box 72, Folder 3)
  - O, 1990s (Box 72, Folder 4)
  - P, 1990s (Box 72, Folder 5)
  - Q, 1990s (Box 72, Folder 6)
  - R, 1990s (Box 72, Folder 7)
  - S, 1990s (Box 72, Folder 8)
  - T, 1990s (Box 72, Folder 9)
  - U, 1990s (Box 72, Folder 10)
  - V, 1990s (Box 72, Folder 11)
  - W, 1990s (Box 72, Folder 12)
  - X, 1990s (Box 72, Folder 13)
  - Y, 1990s (Box 72, Folder 14)
  - Z, 1990s (Box 72, Folder 15)
  - J, 1990-93 (Box 104, Folder 1)
  - L, 1990-93 (Box 104, Folder 2)
  - N, 1990-93 (Box 104, Folder 3)
  - O, 1990-93 (Box 104, Folder 4)
  - Q, 1990-93 (Box 104, Folder 5)
  - R, 1990-93 (Box 104, Folder 6)
  - S, 1990-93 (Box 104, Folder 7)
  - T, 1990-93 (Box 104, Folder 8)
  - U, 1990-93 (Box 104, Folder 9)
  - V, 1990-93 (Box 104, Folder 10)
  - Y, 1990-93 (Box 104, Folder 11)
  - Z, 1990-93 (Box 104, Folder 12)
  - Pacific Bell V. Linkline, 2000s (Box 68, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence File, 2000s (Box 68, Folder 2)
  - Letters & Mails, 2000s (Box 68, Folder 3)
  - A, 2000s (Box 68, Folder 4)
  - B, 2000s (Box 68, Folder 5)
  - C, 2000s (Box 68, Folder 6)
  - D, 2000s (Box 68, Folder 7)
  - E, 2000s (Box 68, Folder 8)
  - F, 2000s (Box 68, Folder 9)
  - G, 2000s (Box 68, Folder 10)
  - H, 2000s (Box 68, Folder 11)
  - I, 2000s (Box 57, Folder 1)
  - J, 2000s (Box 57, Folder 2)
  - K, 2000s (Box 57, Folder 3)
  - L, 2000s (Box 57, Folder 4)
  - M, 2000s (Box 57, Folder 5)
  - N, 2000s (Box 57, Folder 6)
  - O, 2000s (Box 57, Folder 7)
  - P, 2000s (Box 57, Folder 8)
  - Q, 2000s (Box 57, Folder 9)
  - R, 2000s (Box 57, Folder 10)
  - S, 2000s (Box 57, Folder 11)
  - U, 1989 (Box 58, Folder 1)
  - T, 2000s (Box 58, Folder 2)
  - U, 2000s (Box 58, Folder 3)
  - V, 2000s (Box 58, Folder 4)
  - W, 2000s (Box 58, Folder 5)
  - X, 2000s (Box 58, Folder 6)
  - Y, 2000s (Box 58, Folder 7)
  - Z, 2000s (Box 58, Folder 8)
  - XYZ, 1989 (Box 58, Folder 9)
  - Memos(1), 1989 (Box 58, Folder 10)
  - Memos(2), 1989 (Box 58, Folder 11)
  - V, 1989 (Box 58, Folder 12)
- Series XII. Statements & Testimonies
  - Clipping 1972, 1972 (Box 107, Folder 1)
  - Clipping 1973, 1973 (Box 107, Folder 2)
  - Clipping 1974, 1974 (Box 107, Folder 3)
  - Clipping 1975, 1975 (Box 107, Folder 4)
  - Clipping 1976, 1976 (Box 107, Folder 5)
  - Clipping 1977, 1977 (Box 107, Folder 6)
  - Clipping 1978, 1978 (Box 107, Folder 7)
  - Clipping 1979, 1979 (Box 107, Folder 8)
  - Clipping 1980, 1980 (Box 107, Folder 9)
  - Clipping 1981, 1981 (Box 107, Folder 10)
  - Clipping 1982, 1982 (Box 107, Folder 11)
  - Clipping 1983, 1983 (Box 107, Folder 12)
  - Clipping 1984, 1984 (Box 107, Folder 13)
  - Clipping 1985, 1985 (Box 107, Folder 14)
  - Clipping 1986, 1986 (Box 107, Folder 15)
  - Clipping 1987, 1987 (Box 107, Folder 16)
  - Clipping 1988, 1988 (Box 107, Folder 17)
  - APS XE Phoenix 4/1/86, 1986 (Box 51, Folder 1)
  - Salzburg Award Syracuse University 4/2/86, 1986 (Box 51, Folder 2)
  - Speech ILR School Cornell 4/16/86, 1986 (Box 51, Folder 3)
  - Speech ABA Meeting Washington 4/11/86, 1986 (Box 51, Folder 4)
  - Speech OSU Columbus, Ohio 4/17/86, 1986 (Box 51, Folder 5)
  - Testimony OPPD Rebuttal 4/25/86, 1986 (Box 51, Folder 6)
  - Cornell Symposium Washington, DC 5/20/86, 1986 (Box 51, Folder 7)
  - Speech Wisconsin Tele. Asso. Lake Geneva 5/21/86, 1986 (Box 51, Folder 8)
  - Speech Telecom. Conf. Raleigh 5/28/86, 1986 (Box 51, Folder 9)
  - Speech EEI San Francisco 6/4/86, 1986 (Box 51, Folder 10)
  - Speech Regional Airlines Asso., DC 6/17/86, 1986 (Box 51, Folder 11)
  - Article Yale J of Reg - July, 1986, 1986 (Box 51, Folder 12)
  - Speech GTE Hot Springs, VA 7/7/86, 1986 (Box 51, Folder 13)
  - NERA Antitrust Seminar Santa Fe 7/10/86-7/12/86, 1986 (Box 51, Folder 14)
  - Testimony ICC Railroad Adequacy Review 7/31/86, 1986 (Box 51, Folder 15)
  - Testimony Commonwealth Edison 8/1/86, 1986 (Box 51, Folder 16)
  - Testimony Central Vermont - Sept., 1986, 1986 (Box 51, Folder 17)
  - Speech NYSEG Cooperstown 9/9/86, 1986 (Box 51, Folder 18)
  - Speech Penn State State College 10/1/86-10/2/86, 1986 (Box 51, Folder 19)
  - Testimony APS XE - June, 1987, 1987 (Box 52, Folder 1)
  - Talk Air Transport Labor Relations Wash., DC 6/17/87, 1987 (Box 52, Folder 2)
  - Speech O&R Utilities Nyack, NY 6/23/87, 1987 (Box 52, Folder 3)
  - Article Bell Atlantic Quar. Based on Wharton - July, 1987, 1987 (Box 52, Folder 4)
  - Speech NERA Antitrust Conf. Santa Fe, NM - July, 1987, 1987 (Box 52, Folder 5)
  - Testimony House Subcommitte on Telecommunications 7/15/87, 1987 (Box 52, Folder 6)
  - Testimony East/West Airlines Australia - August, 1987, 1987 (Box 52, Folder 7)
  - Speech P.S. of New Mex., Santa Fe 8/31/87, 1987 (Box 52, Folder 8)
  - Verified Statement - Oct., 1987, 1987 (Box 52, Folder 9)
  - Speech AT&T Austin, TX 10/5/87, 1987 (Box 52, Folder 10)
  - WRG Meeting Washington, DC 10/6/87-10/7/87, 1987 (Box 52, Folder 11)
  - Testimony NWBell Iowa - Oct., 1987, 1987 (Box 52, Folder 12)
  - Testimony Bell South 10/16/87, 1987 (Box 52, Folder 13)
  - Testimony U.S.Senate Subcommittee on Aviation 11/4/87, 1987 (Box 52, Folder 14)
  - Speech McNaughton Sympos. Washington, DC 11/4/87, 1987 (Box 52, Folder 15)
  - Testimony Connecticut Cable 11/13/87, 1987 (Box 52, Folder 16)
  - Rebuttal Testimony NW Bell Iowa - Nov., 1987, 1987 (Box 52, Folder 17)
  - Testimony Bell South Reply 12/1/87, 1987 (Box 52, Folder 18)
  - Paper AEA Conference "Surprises of Airline Deregulation" 12/28/87, 1987 (Box 52, Folder 19)
  - Seposition ETSI Wash, DC 1/4/88-1/6/88, 1988 (Box 52, Folder 20)
  - Testimony GE (Kentucky Ind. Utility) 2/8/88, 1988 (Box 52, Folder 21)
  - From NY/NJ Power Authority New York City 2/18/88, 1988 (Box 52, Folder 22)
  - Speech&Talk U. Houston Houston, TX 2/25/88, 1988 (Box 52, Folder 23)